<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on Children COVIDraw</title>
    <link>/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on Children COVIDraw</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ages</title>
      <link>/work/ages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/ages/</guid>
      <description>The representation of illness according to the ages of childrens Context
To understand how children represent this epidemic, it is essential to understand how they conceptualize illness. Previous studies suggest that children&amp;rsquo;s conceptualization of illness is complex and their understanding of health problems undergoes important developmental changes as a function of their cognitive skills (1).
By age 5, children picture diseases as germs, faces, or irregular, monster-like shapes. At this age, children are aware of the contagious nature of illnesses such as the common cold (2,3) and report being afraid of getting sick while playing with other children in the playground (4).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawings illnesses</title>
      <link>/work/modern-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/modern-hospital/</guid>
      <description>Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19</title>
      <link>/work/cargo-terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/cargo-terminal/</guid>
      <description>Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>